目 前 资 金
最 新 余 额
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
打工
姐妹花
第十一集
第三季
打工
姐妹花
第十一集
第三季
翻校  我是男的赛太公
翻校  没欺负人YY猫
后期  灰灰是菇凉
时间轴 总监  没欺负人YY猫
停止计时
And, time.
37分钟
37 minutes,
从家里出发  到坐上地铁
we got from the apartment to the subway,
最后到达学校  又刷新记录了
to the pastery school in record time.
虽然我来不及穿胸罩
I mean, I'm not wearing a bra,
而且丁字裤好像也前后穿反了
and my thong might be on backwards.
丁字裤怎么会穿反呢
There is no wrong way to wear a thong,
只要不舒服就对了
as long as it's uncomfortable.
而且你穿胸罩也只是摆设而已
And with you, the bra is just for decoration.
而我是必须得穿
I have to wear one because you get a ticket
"孩子"不放安全座椅上  是要吃罚单的
for not put the kids in a car seat.
教室见  我得先跟我老婆道别
See you in class guys, I gotta say good bye to my wife.
你真以为我要跟你吻别吗
You think I was gonna kiss you?
对啊
Yes.
我是你老婆  你是我那位
I'm the wife, you are the husband
某天被我发现你有异装癖
who I caught wearing my cloth one day,
但我却没戳穿的老公
but I don't say anything about it.
早安啊  二位
Morning, guys.
早安  碧碧
Oh, hi, Bebe.
见到我很惊讶吧
Surprised to see me, right?
大家总以为我会在夜半时分自杀
Everyone always thinks I'm not gonna make it through the night,
但我还活着  连我自己都惊讶
but here I am, even surprised myself.
跟一个随时会崩溃的人
What's it like working in an office
在同一间办公室工作是什么感觉呢
with someone who's about to snap like a breadstick?
绝对没想象中这么有趣
Not as much fun as you'd think.
但碧碧人很好  而且在这工作
But Bebe's sweet, and working here
主要是为了替你挣学费
is putting you through pastry school.
-好啦  再见  -再见
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
-我要离婚  -早去申请了
- I want a divorce. - I already filed.
老婆  我要五块钱
Hey, wife, I need $5
赔昨天弄坏的工具
to pay for a spatula I broke yesterday.
我昨天突然戈登・拉姆齐上身了
I was having a Gordon Ramsay moment.
戈登・拉姆齐  英国知名厨师与电视名人
脾气火爆  时常骂人
有机会我不介意跟他睡哦
I'd have sex with him, by the way.
为啥  他肯定也是会吼你
Why? He'd just be yelling at you
然后说你"做"错了
and telling you you're doing it wrong.
做爱不都这样吗
Yeah, sex.
拿吧  钱在我包里
Take it. It's in my purse.
碧碧  你有偷偷不吃的药吗
Yo, Bebe, you got any extra pills you're not taking?
没有  我全都有吃
No, I'm taking them all.
老天爷  别啊
Oh, my God, no.
干嘛  我也就想要个一颗  两颗
What? I just wanted one. Or two.
就想减减压
Just to take the edge off.
三点我有一场生奶油考试
I have a whipped cream final at 3:00.
是报纸里的讣告
No. In the obituaries.
我认识这个人
I know this person.
"安东尼娅・佛罗伦蒂诺  享年八十
"Antonia Florentino, 80,
在睡梦中安详过世"
Died peacefully in her sleep."
明显是自杀嘛  对吧
That's a suicide, right?
她是我的保姆
She was my nanny.
你现在还有保姆啊
You still have a nanny?
真幸福
Lucky.
我小时候大多数时间都是她带大的
She took care of me most of my childhood.
我好爱她
I loved her so much.
节哀
So sorry.
我对我的老邻居卡拉
That's kind of how I felt
也有这种感觉
about my old neighbor, Carla.
虽然她没有养育我
I mean, she didn't take care of me,
但在我小的时候  她都允许我
but when I was a kid, she used to let me
喝她家花园水管的水
drink out of her hose.
我最后一次见安东尼娅  是她载我
The last time I saw Antonia, she was driving me
和邋遢鬼妮莉・费塔朵一起去参加青少年选择奖
and a sloppy Nelly Furtado to the Teen Choice Awards.
妮莉・费塔朵加拿大女歌手  曾赢得过青少年选择奖
现在可以在办公室里哭了吗
Oh, are we allowed to cry at work now?
我一般只在车里哭
'cause I only do it in my car.
麦克斯  你知道我意识到什么吗
Max, you know what I just realized?
这是我保姆死后  我第一次走进这家餐厅
This is the first time I've been here since my nanny died.
这话你已经在墨西哥快餐店说过了
You just said that at Chipotle.
然后十分钟后  你又说了一遍
And then you said it again ten minutes later,
也是在那家快餐店
also at chipotle.
有点同情心好吗
Show some sensitivity.
我当时哭是因为我保姆死了
I was crying because my nanny died.
也因为我们悼念的早午餐是在一家快餐店
And also because our grief brunch was at Chipotle.
卡洛琳  你的保姆过世啦
Caroline, your nanny passed?
我深表同情  宝贝  太遗憾了
My sympathies, sweetheart. That's a shame.
但没有什么比黑人葬礼更棒的了
But there is nothing better than a black funeral.
我1984年时参加了我爷爷的葬礼  至今宿醉未醒
I'm still hung over from my grandpa's in '84.
厄尔  我的保姆是白人
Earl, my nanny was white.
你的保姆居然是白人
Your nanny was white?
小姑娘  你的确是富二代啊
Child, you were rich.
你看见阿憨了吗
Have you seen Han?
葬礼明天在费城举行
The funeral's in Philadelphia tomorrow,
我得跟他请一天假
and I need the day off.
我之前好像看见他了
Well, I think I saw him earlier.
但话说回来  那也有可能是一只猫
But then again, it might have been a cat.
我们俩都需要请一天假
Hey, we both need the day off.
我要陪你去  无论是出于精神支持
I'm going with you for moral support/
还是为了吃第一个费城牛肉三明治
my first cheesesteak/
或我想使劲甩独立钟里面的那个大球
I want to ride the liberty bell like a wrecking ball.
我刚在《科技新时代》看到一篇超级疯狂的文章
I just read the craziest article in this Popular Science
是关于"白矮"星  黑"洞"和天王星[你屁眼]
about White Dwarfs, black holes, and Uranus.
不对  让我重新说一遍
Oh, no. Let me start over.
阿憨  我们明天要请假  我保姆过世了
Han, we need tomorrow off. My nanny died.
她就像是我的母亲
She was like a mother to me.
但她不是你的母亲
But she was not your mother.
餐厅有明确的规定
And diner rules clearly state
必须是自己家人的葬礼才能请假
you can only take off for the death of a family member.
餐厅还规定不许在上班时候喝酒呢
Well, the rules also say no drinking on the job,
但现在
but...
好吧  你可以去
Okay, yes, you can go.
因为在我们国家
Because in my culture,
对长辈是十分尊敬的
it's important to honor the elderly.
我跟一位97的老人同睡上下铺
I shared a bunk bed with a 97-year-old
一直睡到我22岁呢
till I was 22.
敢问你是在"上面"还是"下面"
Were you on the top or bottom?
我向来是在下面啊
Oh, I was always the bottom.
不对  让我重新说一遍
Oh, no. Let me start over.
卡洛琳
Hey, Caroline.
我收到你保姆过世的短信了
I got your nanny death text.
所以我出于尊重  穿上了一身黑
So I'm wearing black out of respect.
而且  刚好我的月事也来了
And also, I got my period.
谢谢  苏菲  太有爱了
Thanks, Sophie. That's lovely.
是吗  哪部分
It is? Which part?
在波兰  我保姆死的时候
You know, back in Poland when my nanny died,
我心都碎了  难过得都吃不下她了
I was so heartbroken, I could barely eat her.
你居然吃你死掉的保姆
You ate your dead nanny?
山羊终究是动物
Well, a goat's a goat.
称呼改变不了本质
It doesn't matter what you name it.
它仍是美味的羊肉
It's still good goat meat.
好了  我去我卡座里坐着了
All right, I'll be in my booth.
一份金枪鱼三明治和三颗痛经药  谢谢
I'm going to order a tuna melt and three Midol, please.
等等  我们要怎么去费城啊
Wait, how are we gonna get there?
碧碧说她有车  我们可以问问她
Oh, Bebe said she had a car, we can just ask her.
我不想跟她坐同一辆车
I don't want to get in a car with her.
我连跟她说话都不想
I don't even want to get in a conversation with her.
我可以载你们去
I can drive you.
但我们得先去我巴克斯县的姐姐家
We just have to stop at my sister's in Bucks County,
拿一个没有任何标记的包裹
pick up an unmarked package,
然后再送到康乃迪克州
and swing by Connecticut to drop it off.
奥列格  这个包裹里有违法的东西吗
Oleg, is there anything illegal about this delivery?
没有  只是几双鞋
No, it's just some shoes...
里面塞满可卡因而已
stuffed with cocaine.
对了  鞋子是用印度大麻做的哦
Also the shoes are made of hashish.
我还是打给碧碧好了
I'll call Bebe.
好吧  但我要坐后座
Okay, but I'm sitting in the back
因为我不想沾染到她的疯气
'cause I don't want the crazy to get on me.
碧碧  你送我们去葬礼
Bebe, I can't thank you enough
真是太感谢你了
for driving us to the funeral.
现在车速才20迈  其实你可以开快点的
We're only going 20. You can go faster if you want.
是啊  刚有一棵树超过了我们
Yeah, we just got passed by a tree.
你那只爱放屁和神经紧张的可卡犬
And I'm especially thrilled your nervous cocker spaniel
也跟着来  真让我尤为振奋
with gas and hot spots got to join us.
够了  你现在都开到100迈了
Okay, now you're going 100.
其实你可以开慢点的
We can go slower if you want.
抱歉  我的专长是做事极端
Sorry. Extremes-- that's my thing.
有一次我搬家到东京住了一天
One time I moved to Tokyo for a day.
-麦克斯  又来了  -我知道
- Max, it just hit me again. - I know.
貌似她给那只狗吃了西兰花
It's like she feeds him broccoli.
不是啦
No.
是我又想到安东尼娅真的去世了
That Antonia is really dead.
好消息是  根据点评网
Well, the good news is, according to Yelp,
她葬礼距离最出名的那家
she's dead about two blocks
费城牛肉奶酪三明治只有两个街区
From the famous philly cheesesteak place.
麦克斯  放尊重点行吗
Max, show some respect.
我又不认识她
Well, I didn't know her.
老实说  我只当她是帮我和牛肉三明治
In fact, I only know her as the lady who brought me
牵红线的媒人
and cheesesteaks together.
即使我们从未见过面  但对于安东尼娅的家人来说
Even though we've never met, it'll mean so much
我的出席对他们来说意义重大
to Antonia's family that I came out of respect.
对我的心理医生来说也意义重大
It'll mean so much to my therapist
因为我离开我的安全区
that I left my safe zone
还只带了一条狗
and only brought one of the dogs.
麦克斯  你觉得除了我的悼词之外
Max, do you think in addition to my eulogy,
我还应该念几段我儿时的日记吗
I should read something from my childhood journal?
不应该  但我觉得你还是会执意念
I don't, but I think you're gonna do it anyway.
"1997年  圣诞节早上
"Christmas morning, 1997.
安东尼娅用一杯热可可和一根我最爱的
Antonia woke me up with a cup of hot cocoa
薄荷棒棒糖叫醒我
and my favorite peppermint stick,
然后我们开始拆礼物"
and then we opened presents."
1997年  圣诞节早上
Christmas morning, 1997.
我冲我妈脸上泼了一杯冰水
I threw cold water on my mother's face.
直到元旦那天  她人还是没反应
New year's day-- still no movement.
这是我手上唯一一张我们的合影
This is the only picture I still have of us.
那是我们一起过的第一个万圣节
It was our first Halloween together.
我当时四岁
I was four.
瞧她给我做的那身可爱的小鸡装束
Look at that cute little baby chick costume she made me.
唧唧  唧唧
Peep, peep.
真可爱
Aw, so cute.
看车
Car.
我从来没穿过万圣节服装
I never had a Halloween costume.
我通常是把头发乱糟糟地扎起来
I used to put my hair in a messy bun
然后跌跌撞撞地挨家挨户敲门
and stumble from door-to-door
告诉大家我就是我妈
telling people I was my mother.
今年万圣节  我打扮成我的医生迈克
This Halloween, I went as my doctor, Michael.
我把我的狗狗打扮成
And I dressed up my buddy here
他的爱人  约瑟夫
As his lover, Joseph.
我们后来情不自禁
We lost.
安东尼娅一直陪在我身边
Antonia was always there for me--
万圣节  圣诞节  复活节  每一个节日
Halloween, Christmas, Easter-- every holiday.
每一天
Really, every day.
她就像我妈妈一样
She was really like a mother to me.
那你真正的妈妈呢
Where was your real mother?
这只是什么品种的狗啊
Hey, what kind of dog is that?
除了"苦瓜脸品种"外
I mean, besides "Sad"?
她妈妈跟人偷情  然后被扫地出门
Her mother had an affair, got pushed out.
那是她的痛处  所以别随便碰
That's her hot spot, so don't lick it.
没关系  麦克斯  我不需要任何保护
It's okay, Max, I don't need any protection.
你不需要任何保护[措施]
You don't need protection?
你是谁  跟我约过会的男人吗
Who are you, every guy I've ever dated?
碧碧  没错  我妈妈是背叛了我爸爸
Bebe, yes, my mother was unfaithful to my father,
所以她被赶走了
so she was sent away.
但我有安东尼娅  她照顾我
But I had Antonia and she took care of me.
她就是我的家人
She was my family.
那一定很难熬  人人都需要妈妈
That must have been hard. Everybody needs a mother.
我没有我妈  一定会疯掉的
I'd be crazy without my mother.
我看病都是她载我去的
She drives me to all my appointments.
但你不是会开车吗
But you drive.
是啊
Yeah...
但医生不让我开
But I'm not supposed to.
我让碧碧在车里等着没事吧
It's okay I asked Bebe to wait in the car, right?
她不会憋死的  有扇车窗留了一条缝
I mean, she'll be okay. We cracked a window.
是啊  她有个碗和一个宠物用咀嚼玩具
Yeah, and she's got a bowl and a chew-toy.
来吧  过来签到
Come on, let's sign in.
麦克斯  当我见到她家人时  我要振作
Max, I have to keep it together when I meet the family.
我不能太动情
I can't be all emotional.
瞧  我的手在抖  太可怕了
Look, my hand's shaking. This is terrible.
干嘛  刚才的签名丑死了
What? It was a terrible signature.
而且那页也只有五个其他人的名字而已
And there were only five other names on the page.
处理掉它
Get rid of it.
"处理掉它"
"Get rid of it"?
你是谁  跟我约过会的男人吗
Who are you, every guy I've ever dated?
"卡洛琳・钱宁"
"Caroline Channing."
给  麦克斯
Here, Max.
瞧
Oh, look.
这里的花和一切都好美
The flowers and everything are so beautiful.
好了
There you go.
你居然签"费成・三明智"
You signed "Phil E. Cheesesteak"?
你告诉我不要再提这件事了
You told me not to mention it anymore,
所以那只是个提醒而已
so it's just a reminder.
麦克斯  到时候一定会有很多人
Okay, Max, there are gonna be a lot of people
想要得到我的关注  所以拜托要耐心
who will want my attention, so please be patient
站在我身边  偶尔给我支持的依靠
and stand next to me for the occasional supportive lean.
如果有人开始哭得太夸张
And if someone starts to get too weepy,
立刻把他们从我身上拉开
push them out of the way
因为这条裙子可不能沾上眼泪
because I can't get tears on this dress.
我明天九点前还得退给百货公司
It has to be back to Barneys by 9:00 A.M.
你来了
You're here.
开始了  麦克斯
Here we go, Max.
我刚是跟他说话
I was talking to him.
当然当然  今天对我们来说都很伤心
Of course you were. It's a very sad day for us all.
真是太伤了
That was rough.
麦克斯  看
Max, look.
这就是安东尼娅
This is Antonia.
她看起来人很好
She looks really nice.
的确
She was.
原来她还在军队待过
I didn't know she was in the military.
美军规定床单要掖进床垫下  四个角要折成45度
难怪床单四个边角弄得那么利落
But it does explain those fabulous bed sheet corners.
等等  你居然不知道你的保姆是海军吗
Wait, you didn't know your nanny was a marine?
真是太糟糕了  如果是我就会炫耀
That's too bad, 'cause I'd be all,
"喂  其他有钱的小屁孩
"Yo, other little rich kid!
老娘的保姆能轻易折断你们脖子哦"
My nanny can snap your neck."
瞧  那俩是她的姐妹  塞西莉亚和安吉拉
Oh, look. There are her sisters, Cecelia and Angela,
这几个是她的侄子和侄女
and there are her nieces and nephews.
这些照片居然没一张有我
And there is not me anywhere.
我的照片肯定跟其他重要人物
You know, my picture must be in the coffin
一起放在棺材里
With the other V.I.P.S.
如果你是个重要人物  能叫人上酒吗
If you're a V.I.P., can we get some bottle service?
下午好  女士们
Good afternoon, ladies.
我是安东尼  安东尼娅的侄子
I'm Anthony, Antonia's nephew.
真是令人难过的一天
It's sad day, huh?
没错
Yes, it is.
我觉得我现在也没这么难过了
Think I just got a little less sad.
安东尼
Oh! Anthony!
住手  我们可是一家人
Stop. We're family.
我是卡洛琳・钱宁
I'm Caroline Channing.
我只知道你是卡洛琳辣妹
You're Caroline "Hot," is all I know.
你们俩是要用信封装钱
You ladies need cash envelopes
还是要不要都行
or you guys cool?
我最缺的就是装钱的信封了
I always need a cash envelope.
抱歉  信封要拿来装什么啊
I'm sorry, envelopes for what?
根据意大利葬礼的习俗  哀悼者瞻仰死者遗容后
Well, at Italian wakes, the mourners give the family
会捐一点钱给死者家属
a donation after they view the deceased.
所以是要"按次收费"瞻仰吗
So it's pay-per-view?
这句吐槽太犀利了
That was a good one.
晚点要一起喝一杯吗
Hey, you want to go get a pop later?
我们完事就走了  但好吧  安东尼
We're leaving right after, but yes, Anthony.
谢谢  麻烦给我们个信封
Thank you. We'll take an envelope.
遗体就在前面
The body's right through there.
一直往前走
Go right ahead.
安东尼  住手
Anthony, stop.
我真的好紧张啊
I'm really nervous.
我以前从来没见过尸体
I've never seen a dead body before.
我见多了
I've seen a bunch.
有几具还是拜我所赐
A couple of them were my fault.
我没有现金
I don't have any cash.
-你有带钱吗  -我看看我的钱包
- Do you have any money? - Let me check my wallet.
这是名牌密封塑胶袋  可不是什么山寨货哦
This is a real Ziploc, not one of those knock-offs.
一定要把信封封好
Make sure you seal the envelope,
好让别人觉得里面都是25美分的硬币
so people think it's all quarters.
麦克斯  下一个到我们了
Max, we're next.
我好害怕  牵住我的手
I'm afraid. Hold my hand.
牵手  你以为我们是什么
Hold hands? What are we?
基督徒约会网站上第五次约会的男女吗
On a ChristianMingle fifth date?
该网站是最大的信仰性在线约会网站之一
拜托了  麦克斯  我好紧张啊
Please, Max. I'm nervous.
-天啊  -谢谢
- Oh, God. - Thank you.
好了  松手
Okay. Now give it back.
干嘛  这已经是我维持最长的一段感情了
What? That was just my longest relationship.
再说了  我得把这些零钱放进信封里
Plus, I need it to put this change in the envelope.
她看起来一脸平静
Oh, she looks so peaceful.
安东尼娅  我是卡洛琳
Hi, Antonia. It's me, Caroline.
我应该亲她吗  她家人在旁边看着呢
Should I kiss her? The family is right there watching.
前面那个女士就亲了
The lady before us kissed her.
亲吧  反正看样子她也不会推开你
Go for it. Doesn't look like she'd fight you.
好的  数到三
Okay, on the count of three.
一  二
One, two--
不行  麦克斯  牵着我的手
No! Max, hold my hand again while I--
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
住手  别捡了  反正我们也要给她家人的
Wait, leave it! We were giving it to them anyway.
不是全部都给啊  那可是我们买三明治的钱
Not all of it. That's our cheesesteak money.
别捡了  快过来
Leave it. Come on.
刚才的事真是非常抱歉
I am so, so sorry about that.
我实在是太紧张了  你懂的
My nerves got the best of me. You understand.
我是塞西莉亚  安东尼娅的
I'm Cecelia, Antonia's--
妹妹  我知道
Sister. I know.
你们俩长得很像
I see the resemblance.
我是卡洛琳
I'm Caroline.
谁啊  卡洛琳
Caroline who?
卡洛琳・钱宁啊
Oh. Caroline Channing.
谁是卡洛琳・钱宁
Caroline Channing who?
你现在心情不好想不起  可以理解
You're having a hard time processing. Understandable.
今天对我们所有人来说都非常难过
It's been a very emotional day for us all.
这个女孩是谁
Who is this girl?
你  我倒觉得我在哪里见过你
You, I feel like I've seen somewhere.
你是里基在罗彻斯特的女友吗
Are you Ricky's girl From Rochester?
有可能  是的话对我有什么好处
I could be. What's in it for me?
安东尼娅在我小时候照顾过我
Antonia used to take care of me when I was little.
安东尼娅是你的临时保姆啊
Oh, Antonia was your baby-sitter.
你能来真好
Very nice of you to come.
她不是我的"临时保姆"
Well, she was hardly my "baby-sitter."
她十年来的每一天都在照顾我
She took care of me every day for ten years.
我是卡洛琳  卡洛琳・钱宁啊
Caroline. Caroline Channing.
很抱歉  但我真不认识你  亲爱的
I'm sorry, but I don't know who you are, sweetheart,
虽然你一直在向我施压  逼我假装认识你
Though it seems to be what you're hammering me about.
容我失陪一下
If you'll excuse me,
我要去抽根烟
I need a cigarette.
抽完了我还得去捡
And then I got to remove
掉在我姐姐身上的钢G
some of those pennies off of my sister.
那是口棺材  不是什么许愿井
It's a coffin, not a wishing well.
这个葬礼变得好令人感到沉重[沮丧]
This funeral turned out to be very depressing.
没错
Well, yeah.
有个死人躺在这里  不死气沉沉都难
Dead body in the room, generally a buzz-kill.
除非这是爱尔兰式守灵
Unless it's an Irish wake--
这样你就可以隔着棺材玩啤酒乒乓啦
then you're playing beer pong off the coffin.
爱尔兰人爱喝酒  啤酒乒乓是一种喝酒游戏
我的意思是  这家人
No, I mean, how is it possible
怎么可能没一个人认识我呢
that the family doesn't even know me?
难道安东尼娅从来没提起过我吗
Did Antonia never even mention me?
你应该往好的方面想
Let's focus on the positive.
安东尼真的很喜欢你的小屁屁
Anthony really liked your ass.
我知道我和安东尼娅拥有过什么
I know what Antonia and I had.
这就是我们拥有的回忆
This is what we had.
唧唧  唧唧
Peep, peep.
那是我们的美好回忆
That's what we had.
那已经很多啦
Well, that's a lot.
但我猜这家人不会承认我们的回忆
But I guess no one in this family wants to admit that,
这真是太遗憾了
and it's a shame too,
因为我准备了很棒的悼词
because I had a great eulogy.
是吗
You do?
是的  没错
Yes. I do.
你想让我跟你分享吗
Would you like me to share it with you?
当然想啊
I most certainly would.
你不是真的要拿你的烂悼词
You are not seriously eulogy-bombing
去精神轰炸那位老太太吧
that old lady, are you?
是她先问起我的悼词的
She asked me about my great eulogy.
她都一百岁了
She's a hundred.
很可能听成你说你有一位很棒的泌尿科医生
She probably thought you said you had a great urologist.
你有笔吗
Do you have a pen?
我要记下她医生的名字
I'm getting the name of her doctor.
不  夫人  我说的不是"泌尿科医生"
No, ma'am, I didn't say, "urologist."
我说的是"悼词"  很棒的悼词[音似]
I said, "eulogy." A great eulogy.
你凭啥上去念悼词啊
Why would you give the eulogy?
因为我是卡洛琳・钱宁
Because I'm Caroline Channing.
谁呀
Who?
卡洛琳・钱宁
Caroline Channing.
安东尼娅是我的保姆
Antonia was my nanny.
我家过去超级有钱
My family was rich,
但后来我父亲骗走了全世界的钱
but then my father robbed everyone,
于是我们沦为害群之马
and we became the scourge of society,
同一周  梅尔・吉布森仇视犹太人的言论
overshadowed a little bit by Mel Gibson
盖过了我家丑闻风头一点点
hating the Jews that same week.
你们绝对应该记得
Surely, you remember?
小宝贝  我连怎么来这里的都不记得了
Honey, I don't even remember how I got here.
真是难以置信
I can't believe this.
我整个童年之所以"快乐"都是因为
I constructed my entire "Happy" Childhood
我坚信  就算我妈离开了我
On the fact that even though my mom left
就算她不爱我
and apparently didn't love me,
但还有安东尼娅爱我
Antonia did.
而我来了这里  我意识到
And now I get here and I realize
没人爱过我  她只是为了挣钱
no one loved me, I was just a paycheck.
我只是她照顾的众多小孩中的一个
One of the many kids she baby-sat.
我甚至不知道我来这里的意义是什么
I don't even know why I bothered to come.
我去一趟洗手间  然后我们就走
I'm going to the restroom and then we can just leave.
打扰一下  你好
Excuse me. Hi.
我是麦克斯  里基的女友
Max, Ricky's girl.
我知道现在你很难过
I know this is a hard time for you,
但对我朋友来说  她也很难过
but it's a hard time for my friend as well.
即使你从来没有听说过她
And even though you never heard of her,
但我恳请你能否过去
I was wondering if you could just go over there,
对她说你想起来了
and say you just remembered her,
安东尼娅经常在你们面前提起她
and that Antonia talked about her all the time?
我明白这是要你说谎推翻你之前的话
I know it's a 180 on your original story and a lie,
我也乐意给你辛苦费
and I'd offer to pay you for your trouble,
但我的养老金全在装着你姐姐的盒子里了
but my 401k is laying in that box on top of your sister.
我是看在你男人里基的面子  才没赶你俩走
Look, I only permitted you two to stay
要不是去年乔舅舅从楼顶摔下来时
'cause your Ricky was so nice to uncle Joe
全靠他出手相救
when he fell off the roof last year.
但现在  你们还是离开这吧
But now, you gotta go.
好吧  随便你好了
Okay. Be that way.
但下次乔舅舅要去做透析时  里奇不会去接他的
But don't expect Ricky to pick up Uncle Joe for dialysis.
麦克斯  你这是干什么
Max, what are you doing?
是那家人让我贴上去的
The family asked me to put it up.
他们想起你来了
They just remembered you.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我有这么可悲吗  需要你粘照片
I'm so pathetic, you have to put up my picture
来哄我吗
to make me feel better?
在某种程度上  是的
In a way, yes.
这照片本来就应该贴在这里
It belongs up there.
谁不想会认识这个孩子啊
Who wouldn't want to know that kid?
很高兴见到你  安东尼娅
Nice to meet you, Antonia.
千万不要做鬼来找我们
Please don't haunt us.
快上路吧  我们还要买牛肉三明治呢
Now, let's hit the road and get some freaking cheesesteaks!
麦克斯  快把照片弄下来
Max, please take that down.
太丢脸了
It's so embarrassing.
这里没人认识我
Nobody here knows anything about me.
他们也不认识我啊  小鸡仔
They didn't know me either, chicken.
你叫谁小鸡仔呢
Hey, who you callin' chicken?
我  那是安东尼娅给我起的昵称
Me. That was Antonia's nickname for me.
你知道我是谁吗
You know who I am?
我当然知道
Of course I do.
安东尼娅的小鸡仔  她的小唧唧
Antonia's little chick, her peep.
她很爱你
She loved you.
她也喜欢给你做那套装束
And she loved making you that costume.
整个厨房餐桌上全铺满了亮片
Took the whole kitchen table up with all those sequins,
她知道你就该是最耀眼的那一个
But she knew you deserved to sparkle.
她非常爱你  我根本没办法抱怨
She loved you so much, I couldn't begin to complain.
不好意思  请问您是哪位
I'm so sorry. What was your name?
我是梅格・欧哈拉  我是她的室友
I'm Meg O'Hara. I was her roommate.
兼爱人
And lover.
我们在一起30年了
We were together 30 years.
军队拉拉情
The military!
没错  明眼人一看就知道了
I know, right? I mean, come on.
当时在坦克那  我的手可是搂着她啊
That's me with my arm around her on that tank.
而那一家子蠢蛋却还是看不出来
And the family still had no clue.
老一代蕾丝边  超级酷啊
Vintage lez-- very cool.
安东尼娅会希望你收下这些照片
I know Toni would have wanted you to have these.
感谢你的到来  小鸡仔
Oh, thanks for coming, chicken.
你大概是这世界上唯一一个
You're probably the only person in the world
对她的爱像我一样纯粹的人了
who loved her as purely as I did.
麦克斯  看
Max, look.
圣诞节的照片
Christmas.
我生日时的照片
And my birthday.
还有参加青少年选择奖时的照片
And the Teen Choice Awards.
节哀顺变
I'm sorry for your loss.
感激不尽
Thank you.
费城牛肉奶酪三明治  人人有份啦
Philly cheesesteaks for everybody!
我终于活过来了
And you really haven't lived
之前在雪弗兰里跟九个牛肉三明治
until you've driven two hours in a Chevy
和一只爱放屁的动物待了两个小时  都要死了
with nine cheesesteaks and a gassy animal.
这有啥  我不就在车上吃完了
What? I ate mine in the car.
厄尔  你错过了一场精彩的葬礼
Hey, Earl, you missed one hell of a funeral.
你真应该去的
You should have come.
那有不少八九十岁的老辣奶
There were some hot octogenarians,
而且我接收到其中一位超强的"求欢"信号
and I got a definite "jungle fever" vibe from one of them.
像我这种年纪的人  可不想在葬礼上出现
Girl, at my age, you don't go anywhere near funerals.
只要你一不小心打个瞌睡  就得花上六小时
You accidentally doze off, you spend six hours
把你自己从地里挖出来
digging yourself out of the ground.
你还好吧  小鸡仔
Hey, how you holding up, chicken?
我没事  多谢关心
I'm okay. Thanks.
麦克斯  我死的时候
And Max, when I die,
我不在乎我的葬礼都有谁出席
I don't care who else is at my funeral,
只要你来了就行
as long as you're there.
我当然会去
Of course I'll be there.
凶手向来为了甩掉警察而出席葬礼
The murderer always shows up to throw off the cops.
对了  棺材别花太多钱
Also, save the money on a casket
给我一套迪奥寿服  化烟熏妆  扔洞里就行了
and just toss me in a hole wearing Dior and a smoky eye.
如果到时我很胖  那就火葬了吧
Unless I'm fat-- then burn me.
我不想要葬礼
Well, I don't want a funeral.
等我死的时候  把我尸体塞进大炮里
When I die, just shove my corpse into a cannon
直接冲着大西洋城特朗普赌场来一发  送我过去
and blow me directly into the Trump casino.